Sol Gorelick WAG 019
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
Sol Gorelick Papers
undated
WAG 019
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
19.0 linear feet (19 boxes)
Scope and Contents note
Papers related to Social Service Employees Union, Local 371.
- Abortion: Flyers, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Ad Hoc Committee for a New Progressive Social Work Organization, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Ad Hoc Committee for Collective Bargaining, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Addresses, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Adelphi University; correspondence, transcripts for Sol Gorelick (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Adelphi University Alumni Association (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Adelphi University: Student course work (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Advisory Council on Public Welfare, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO (Box 1, Folder 9)
- AFSCME (Box 1, Folder 10)
- American Lung Association, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- American lung Association: "Basic Documents" (Agreement, Policy and Guidelines Manual), 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- American Lung Association: 75th Anniversary Celebration Committee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- American Lung Association: Symposium on Occupational Hazards to the Lungs, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- American Public Welfare Association, 1966; 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- American Public Welfare Association (Box 1, Folder 16)
- American Public Welfare Association (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Americans Against Union Control of Government (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Appeals for Donations (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Anti-Nuclear (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Association for National Welfare Reform, Self-help guide for the poor on Social Services...in New York City (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Association for National Welfare Reform: Social Services and Public Assistance Self-help Guide, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Association of Jewish Employees (Department of Welfare), 1963;1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Association of Supervisors of the Department of Welfare, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Association of Neighborhood Councils, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Association of Supervisors of the Department of Welfare, 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Association of Supervisors of the Department of Welfare; clippings, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Association of Supervisors of the Department of Welfare; correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Association of Supervisors of the Department of Welfare; correspondence (recieved), 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Association of Supervisors of the Department of Welfare; membership committee, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Association of Supervisors of the Department of Welfare; salary appeals, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Association of Supervisors of the Deparment of Welfare; Seminar on Administration, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Brooklyn Committee of One Thousand, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Brooklyn Ethical Meeting House, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn Friends of the Labor Research Association (LRA), 1939;1941;1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn Independent Voters Association, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn People's Action Conference, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association, 1971-1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association, 1969-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association, 1974; 1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- American Lung Association Bulletin, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Brooklyn People's Action Coalition, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Allied Health Professionals Symposium, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Disease; Annual Meeting, 1977;1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Board of Directors, 1972; 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Brooklyn Breathing Partners, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Brooklyn Lung Center Development Committee, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Budget, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Buildings, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Certificate of Incorporation and By-Laws, undated; 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Clippings, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Committee to evaluate the executive director, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Committees and Committee Changes, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Community Health Advisory Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Consumer commission on the accreditation of health services; Conference: Medical Technology and the Health care Consumer, June 19, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Constituent Relations Committee, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Correspondence to Congressman Brasco, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Correspondence with Managing Director (Vera, Anthony), 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; correspondence with Vice President (Mauro, Anthony), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Executive Committee, 1977;1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Finance Committee, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; program of work, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Fund Raising Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; "In Short" newsletter, 1970; 1972; 1978 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Legislative Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Long range planning committee, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; luncheon meeting minutes, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Media Coverage, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Medical Advisory committee, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; National Conference of Executives, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Nominating committee, 1977;1978;1980 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Nursing committee, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Forum: The Psycho-Social Needs of the Chronic Lung Disease Patient, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; publications, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Seminars, 1977;1979 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association; Social Work Advisory Committee, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Brownsville Welfare Brotherhood Committee, 1957-1962 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Brownsville Brotherhood Committee (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Brownsville Community Council, 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Brownsville Consumers Cooperative Society, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Brownsville Council for Social Planning; A Study of the Recreational Facilities of the Brownsville Section of Brooklyn, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Brownsville Boys' Club, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Brownsville Council (Committee) on Youth, 1956-1963 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Brownsville GSS Advisory Council; Title XX Budget Plan, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Brownsville Improvement Group, 1959-1974 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Brownsville Neighborhood Health and Welfare Center, 1954-1956 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Brownsville Social Services Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Brownsville Social Services Center; field staff training, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Brownsville Youth Service Agency, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Bureau of Labor Statistics Report on NYC, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Bureau of Personnel; recruitment program, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Bureau of Public Assistanc; pamphlet: "Interviewing for Staff Selection in Public Welfare, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Bureau of Public Assistance; Thank you card "memo;" Porteus, Vincent, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Bushwick Model center, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Canarsie Youth center; Still Life, youth art journal, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Catalyst (Socialist Journal of the Social Services); press release, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Catholic Home Bureau, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Center for Defense Information, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Center on Social Welfare, Policy and Law, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Center on Social Welfare, Policy and Law; application process for AFDC Benefits; correspondence with NASW, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Central Brooklyn Coordinating Council, 1966;1967;1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Central Brooklyn Mobilization, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Central Brooklyn Talent Search Community Calendar, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Chama Society, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Chaunukah, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Chile, 1974-1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Chile, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Chile, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Chile; newspaper clippings (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Chile, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Chile, 1976-1980 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Chile; Maryann Mahaffet material on her visit to Chile, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Citizens Advisory Committee: Welfare Advocacy Training Program, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Citizens' Committee for Governmental Planning, 1954 (Box 4, Drawer 25)
- Citizens' Party, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- City Employees Union, Local 237, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- City Planning Commission; Gorelick testimony, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Citywide Coalition to Save Our Hospitals, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Citywide Coordinating Committee of Welfare Groups, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Citywide Health Professionals Association, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Civil Liberties, 1963; 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Civil Rights; general, 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Civil Service Merit Council, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Civil Service Technical Guild, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Client Advisory Committee, 1974-1981 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Client-Worker Alliance, undated; 1969 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Clippings; health and hospitals, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Clippings; Welfare, 1960s-1970s (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Cloward, Richard; correspondence, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy; letter, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Coalition for Employment, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Coalition on the Economic Crisis, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Coalition to Fight for Meaningful Jobs; 'Fight for Jobs' conference, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Columbia School of Social Work, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Committee for a Negro Congressman from Brooklyn, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Committee for the fund for Milton Cohen vs HUAC, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Committee for Independent Political Action (CIPA); Greenwich Village, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Committee of the Professions; Social workers for peace, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Committee on Union Responsibility, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Committee to Defend Poor and Working People Against Repression; Security brutality in Jamaica welfare, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Committee to Elect Communist Candidates; 'The Electric Shock: Con Ed's Billion dollar Swindle, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Committee to save the 35 cent far, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Committee Action for Legal Services, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Community Council of Greater New York, 1966-1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Community Council of Greater New York, 1964; 1970-1980 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Community Council of Greater New York: Ad-Hoc Committee on project state levels of AFDC and home relief, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Community Council of Great New York; 'An Alternative to the Welfare Check', 1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Community Council of Greater New York; 'Better Times:' health and welfare weekly newspaper, 1973; 1975 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Community Council of Greater New York; conference on welfare advocacy, 1975; 1977 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Community Council of Greater New York; Face to Face recertification Citizens Monitoring Committee, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Community Council of Greater New York; proposed Human Services Advocacy Center, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Community Council for Greater New York; income maintenance task force, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Community Council for Greater New York; meeting re unemployed minors striken from home relief rolls, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Community Council for Greater New York; 'Network' newsletter, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Community Council for Greater New York; 'Research utilization update' on income maintenance research for public policy, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Community Council for Greater New York; task force on income maintenance, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Community Council for Greater New York; task force on the NYC crisis, 1976; 1979 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Community Council for Greater New York; taske force on welfare issues, public assistance inflation adjustment, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Community Council for Greater New York; 'Title XX: The State Plan' conference, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Community Council for Greater New York; welfare grant increase coalition, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Community Service Society, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Community Service Society; conference on welfare advocacy, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Concered Citizens Committee on Africa, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- CIO pamphlets, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Consumer Health Advocact Committee, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Coordinating Council for Amending the McCarran-Walter Act, 1940s (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Correspondence; general (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Correspondence; appeal to assmblyman re inflation relief, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Correspondence with universities, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Council on municipal reform, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Council of Lung Associations of NY, 1978; 1979 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- The council of the City of New York; task force on welfare issues, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Credit Unions, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Crown Heights, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Crown Heights District Service Council, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Cuba; travel program, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Movie and cultural events; 'Molly Maguire' and 'Sacco and Vanzetti;' cultural politics, undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Datebooks, 1965; 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Death Penalty, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Democratic Party, 1970; 1979; 1980 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Direct action for rights and employment, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- AFSCME, District 37, 1968-1980 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- AFSCME, District 37, 1964-1977 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- AFSCME, District 37, 1960-1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- AFSCME, District Council 1707, 1958; 1965; 1975; 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Department of Health; community service program, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Department of Health, Employment and Welfare; draft of secretary's statement for NY press conference, Feburary 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Department of Income Maintenance (HRA); managment plan, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Department of Income Management, Division of Location and Support; policies and forms, 1974; 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Department of Social Services; McMillan Library, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Department of Social Services; policy recommendations, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Department of Welfare; testimony of Mitchell I. Grinsberg before senate subcommittee on employment, manpower and poverty, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Department of Welfare; 'Three Month Curriculum for New Case Workers', 1967 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Department of Welfare; training and emplpument for mothers in part-time occupations (TEMPO), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- District Council 1707; strike, November 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Downtown Welfare Advocate Center, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Downtown Welfare Advocate Center, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Downtown Welfare Advocate Center; Redistribute America Movement, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- East Flatbush Neighborhood Action Program, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- East new York; general, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Education, 1960-1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- El Salvador, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Ephemera (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Executive Order 10988; The White House, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Experimental Welfare Center Project; progress report, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Father's Day Card, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Fedeal corrupt practices and political activities legislation, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Federal welfare reform proposals, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Fiscal crisis committee, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Food stamps and food distribution, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Fort Greene social services center; complaint regarding functioning of income maintenance unit, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- 4201 Schools for the Deaf and Blind; teacher salaries, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Fulton Citizens Advisory Council; minutes, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Fulton Community Advisory Committee, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Fulton Community Advisory Committee, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Fulton Special Services Center, 1967; 1971; 1974 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Fulton Special Services Center; 'A Typical Day of a Center Director' by Simmon Miller, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Fulton Special Services Center; administrative staff meeting, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Fulton Special Services Center; bomb threat, April 1973 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Fulton Special Services Center; building, 1967; 1973 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Fulton Special Services Center; case lists, 1970; 1971-1972; 1973 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Fulton Special Services Center; cases, 1970; 1971-1972;1973 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Fulton Special Services Center; cultural employment supervisors, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Fulton Special Services Center; client advisory committee, 1966;1975;1979; 1981 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Fulton Special Services Center; community relations, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Fulton Special Services Center; correspondence, 1969; 1972; 1977; 1979 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Fulton Special Services Center; correspondence, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Fulton Special Services Center; correspondence with citizens' committee for children, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Fulton Special Services Center; correspondence with Bureau of Public Assistance Director, 1967-1973 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Fulton Special Services Center; criteria for managerial evaluation, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Fulton Special Services Center; error accountability report, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Fulton Special Services Center; error rate audit, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Fulton Special Services Center; extra departmental facilities: treatment, redicential, ect., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Fulton Special Services Center; eligibility for Face to Face recertification Program Pilot, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Fulton Special Services Center; case statistics, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Fulton Special Services Center; field managers meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Fulton Special Services Center; food stamps, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Fulton Special Services Center; Grace hotel squatters, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Fulton Special Services Center; housing committee, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Fulton Special Services Center; income maintenance for striking union members, 1971; 1972 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Fulton Special Services Center; income managment back logging, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Fulton Special Services Center; local chart (directory), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Fulton Special Services Center; managerial position description, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Fulton Special Services Center; meeting with East NY Community Corporation, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Fulton Special Services Center; memos to staff, 1971;1973 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Fulton Special Services Center; patrol force, 1973; 1978 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Fulton Special Services Center; letter re performance of polic force, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Fulton Special Services Center; Planned Parenthood, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Fulton Special Services Center; procedural memos, 1967-1978 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Fulton Special Services Center; quarterly reports, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Fulton Special Services Center; special tasks and administrative assistant duties, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Fulton Special Services Center; staff, 1967-1976; 1978; 1979 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Fulton Special Services Center; staff assignments, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Fulton Special Services Center; staff committee (black and P.R. celebration), 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Fulton Special Services Center; testimony against Barbara Blum, commissioner of the NYSDSS, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Fulton Special Services Center; misc. training materials, 1972;1973;1975;1976 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Fulton Special Services Center; utilities for public assistance recipients, 1970;1976 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- General, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- General pay plan regulations, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Glauber, Rae, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 75)
- The Greater New York Fund; United Way, 1977; 1979; 1980 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Grey Panthers, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Greenwood Scoail Service Center; closure, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 78)
- Grievances (Box 6, Folder 79)
- Health Education Council of Brooklyn, undated (Box 6, Folder 80)
- Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1965-1967; 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Health Systems Agency of New York City, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Health Systems Agency of New York City, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Hispanic Society of the Department of Social Services, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Hong Kong, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Handwritten chronology of welfare and labor related events, 1953-1957 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Health Systems Agency of NYC; district board 'G', 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Human Resources Administration; Albany bulletin; legislation pertaining to social welfare, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Human Resources Administration; address by Jule M. Sugarman, administrator of HRA NYC, June 30, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Human Resources Administration; Administration for Human Development, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Human Resources Administration; Administrator training Program; Displinary action and hearing procedure, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Human Resources Administration; annual report, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Human Resources Administration; cabinet meetings, 1975; 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Human Resources Administration; Client Advisory Committee Newsletter, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Human Resources Administration; 'Community Affairs Memo' newsletter, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Human Resources Administration; Division of Eligibility Control, 1972; 1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Human Resources Administration; Division of Medical Social Work Services, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Human Resources Administration; executive development meetings, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Human Resources Administration; field staff training program, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Human Resources Administration; Income Managment Center; director's advisory committee, 1970; 1973-1978 (Box 7, Folder 20)